<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<recipe>
<title>
Strawberry Cheesecake In Macaroon Crust
</title>

<category>
  berry, cheesecake, dessert, sweet
</category>

<subtitle>
</subtitle>

<ingredients>
-----SAUCE-----
3 pints Strawberries -- hulled and halved
1/2 cup Sugar
2 tablespoons Fresh lemon juice
-----CRUST-----
1/4 cup Dried apricots -- packed
1/4 cup water
1/3 cup Sugar
2 large Egg whites
1/8 cup Shredded unsweetened coconut -- toasted
-----FILLING-----
1 1/2 pounds Cream cheese -- room temp.
1 1/4 cups Sugar
1/4 teaspoon Salt
3/4 cup Sour cream
1 tablespoon Dark rum
1 tablespoon Fresh lemon juice
2 teaspoons Vanilla extract
3 large Eggs
-----GARNISH-----
1 1/2 pints Strawberries; hulled -- halved
stems intact
Fresh mint sprigs -- optional

</ingredients>

<steps>
SAUCE: Bring all ingredients to boil in heavy large saucepan over high heat.
Reduce heat to medium-low and simmer and mixture has thick syrup consistency, stirring occasional about 1 hour.
Cool. (Can be prepared 2 days ahead. Cover and refrigerate)
CRUST: Bring apricots and water to boil in heavy small saucepan. Cover, remove from heat and let stand until soft about 30 minutes.
Drain apricots and pat dry. Place in processor. Add sugar and egg whites; process until a thick fluffy consistency.
Add 1/2 cup of coconut and process until minced. Transfer mixture to a medium bowl.
Stir in remaining coconut and freeze until firm, about 20 minutes.
Position rack in the center of oven and preheat to 350 degrees F.
Wrap heavy-duty foil around the OUTSIDE of a 9" springform pan with 2 3/4" sides.
Wrap plastic around fingertips and press coconut mixture evenly over the bottom and 2" up sides of pan to form crust.
Instructions:
Bake crust until light brown, about 15 minutes. Remove from oven. Maintain oven temperature.
ILLING:
Instructions:
Using electric mixer, beat cream cheese, sugar and salt in large bowl until smooth.
Add sour cream, rum, lemon juice and vanilla and beat until well blended.
Transfer to crust.
Bake cheesecake until brown, puffed and firm in center, about 1 hour.
Cool cake in pan on rack 10

</steps>
</recipe>
